- Amsterdam , motherfucker . - Okay .
Come on , let 's go . Where are we going ?
Red-light district . Time for sneepur .
Let 's go to the coffee shop first , then get some sneepur .
Hey , I think the Anne Frank house is around here .
Did we come to Europe just to smoke pot ?
I came all the way from Iceland .
- Yeah , what if we did ? - We did that every day in college .
Why not , like , you know , check out a museum ?
No , you 're right . We should go to a museum .
How about the hemp museum ?
Oli proudly presents
Isabella .
She 's cute .
But we can 't rail a girl who 's in a coma .
I think that 's illegal even in Amsterdam .
- Hey , I 'm just warming up , man . - Fucking Oli .
The lcelandic- - Oh , God , how are you ?
You want to get stoned ?
- This will wake you up . - Whatthe fuck ?
This is good Amsterdam shit .
That 's the shit right there , dude .
Trust me .
Yeah .
- lt 's all good , bro . - Yeah , dude , smoke it !
- Dude , what happened ? - Any Dutch people in Amsterdam ?
All right , this is my friend , Josh .
- Well , hello . - Hi .
- Do you guys want another round ? - Yes , okay .
Yeah ?
We will be right back .
- What are you doing ? - What ?
Do you see a single other person in here with a fucking fanny pack ?
Wait . There 's a guy .
Why don 't you go have fanny-pack sex with him
and jizz all over each other 's storage compartments ?
I can 't put my passport in my pocket . It chafes my thighs , bitch .
- All right ? - Yeah .
Where 's Oli ?
He 's fucking genius .
Sneepur alert , 3 o 'clock .
- She smokes . - Dude , it 's Europe !
Every fucking chick smokes . Stop being a pussy .
You are so easy sometimes .
The power of the pack is yours . I 'm out of here .
I 'm sorry .
Yeah , l- - No , I don 't even speak Dutch .
No , I 'm sorry , l- -
Get off me , you fucking faggot-ass elf . Fuck off .
- Hey , what the fuck ? - Hey . Hey .
Come on , faggot .
- Fucker ! - Get your fucking hands off me .
- l 'm an American , I got rights . - Get the fuck out .
- Your fucking club sucks ass , bro . - Kiss my American ass , fucker .
- Fuck you . - Let 's get out of here , bro .
Hey , I don 't know why you guys are waiting .
It 's a fucking fag fest in there . Wall-to-wall fucking cock .
You need one of these to get in , bro . Sorry .
That shit was classic , dude .
He was gonna throw down with a 400-pound Dutchman .
I 'm fucking awesome !
I don 't fucking know what- -
l thought you were a Jew , man . This guy 's a fucking israeli !
You are fucking israeli .
Oh , God , I hope bestiality is legal in Amsterdam
because that girl 's a fucking hog . Look at that , man .
Hey , guys , I think she likes me , man .
Oh , look at that . Josh , my gift to you , man .
Thanks , but paying to do whatever you want to someone isn 't a turn-on .
How are you gonna get over your chick if you don 't bang some new pussy ?
You can 't go home without getting some hot chick .
I agree , but I shouldn 't have to pay for it .
Hey , come on , I 'm paying , man .
Hey .
Are you okay ?
Hello ? Hello ?
Hey , close the door . You watch , you pay .
Sorry . Jesus .
You 're up , slugger .
Man , I 'm fucking- - l 'm tired , man . I can , like , barely stand up .
Josh , you want to be a fucking writer ?
How about some life experience , right there in that room .
- What do we have in here ? - Hey , you watch , you pay .
I pay. I pay , man . Come on .
Hey .
Come , sit .
Your friends are so funny .
Yeah .
You can wash over here , by sink .
It was fine .
What do you mean ? That bitch had the best fucking tits in Amsterdam .
It was fine . It was whatever .
What was that ?
- It 's fucking after curfew , man . - Curfew ? What are we , 1 3 ?
Let us the fuck in , we 're freezing our balls off .
We paid to stay here . They can 't just , like , lock us out .
This is bullshit .
Hello ?
Open the fucking door .
- What did you tell him ? - He just told them to let us in .
- Shut up ! - Jesus .
Shut the fuck up , you fucking Americans .
Hey , I know what to do .
Shut up .
Hey , hey , guys . Up here . Climb quickly .
Come on .
Go . Go , go , go .
Oh , don 't mind them .
They are so fucked up they don 't know what planet they are on .
- Thanks , bro . - It 's no problem .
Not everyone want to kill Americans .
Paxton .
Alexei . But call me Alex .
What 's up , Alex . This is Josh and Oli .
Guys , this is fucking awesome , man .
I 'm the first in line for sneepur .
Oh , that 's Icelandic for " clit . "
Clitoris or clitoris , however you wanna say that .
Women have it .
It 's , like , right near the labia . Like , it hangs .
Oh , yeah . Very good sneepur in Iceland .
- Yeah . - Come on , guys , have a seat .
Where you travel to ?
We started in Paris , which is where we met this drifter .
Anyway , we went all over France
and then Switzerland , Belgium , and now we 're in Amsterdam .
Yeah , kind of over Amsterdam . Way too many Americans .
Yeah , but Oli 's got a friend with a flat in Barcelona
and he 's supposed to hook us up with some hot-ass senoritas .
Looking for girls ?
- Yeah . - Yeah .
So talk to Alex .
He open up the pussy all over the Europe .
I can help you .
Oh , shit . Alex is a pimp , apparently .
Thanks , bro , but I think we 'll be okay .
- Yeah . - Good .
You looking for girls like this ?
These are fucking magnificent .
- Who the hell are these girls ? - You have to go east , my friend .
This is where the best girls are .
The best .
How far east ?
You can go as far as Ukraine , around Odessa .
These girls I met at this one hostel in Slovakia
just outside Bratislava .
The girls there are so hot you cannot believe it .
And they love anyone foreign , especially American .
They hear your accent , they fuck you .
So wait , this place is near Bratislava ?
Josh .
You won 't find this hostel in any guidebook .
Barcelona , so many Americans .
But Slovakia ? No one there .
There is so much pussy , and because of the war , there are no guys .
You go to this hostel , you will have any girl you want .
They go crazy for any foreigner .
You just
take them .
Fuck , man .
Can 't you keep your Viking ass in your pants for , like , two seconds ?
Hey , man , I shaved my ass just for you .
- Okay , all right . - My Viking balls too .
Okay , stop .
I 'm sorry .
My daughter .
She miss her daddy , and Daddy miss her .
Yeah , no problem , dude , it 's cool .
- Saskia . - Cute .
- She 's adorable . - She 's a little cutie , yeah .
This is Sunneva , my daughter .
- Very pretty . - She 's 6 .
She 's starting school this year .
Wait , you have a daughter ?
Yeah , of course , my horse . I was married for eight years .
Okay . All right .
- You are on vacation ? - Yeah , we 're backpacking .
Our next stop is Bratislava .
- What ? - Slovakia .
You will like it .
Casino , girls .
You can pay to do anything .
Anything .
- How are the girls ? - Very beautiful .
They will love you . Handsome American like you .
Handsome devil . He is handsome .
That 's- - That 's awkward . That 's awkward .
That 's awkward too .
- You need a fork there , chief ? - No , no , no .
I prefer to use my hands .
I believe
people have lost their relationship with food .
They do not think :
" This is something who gave its life so I would not go hungry . "
I like to have a connection with something that died for me .
I appreciate it more .
Well , I 'm vegetarian .
And I am a meat-eater .
It 's human nature .
Well , I 'm human , and it 's not in my nature .
Tell me , what is your nature ?
Don 't touch ! Don 't fucking touch me !
I 'm sorry .
Excuse me .
Fucking freak .
Jesus .
Edward Saladhands just groped Josh .
Dude , you finally hooked up . That 's awesome .
Yeah , that 's fucking hilarious .
Or we could visit some factories .
Should be cool .
In this area
we make plastic for Slovakia .
is that so ?
Look at this .
- Nice , eh ? - This is a fucking hostel ?
Holy shit .
You can have that , man . I 'm too scared .
Hey , hey . The party has arrived .
- You are saved from boredom . - Let me guess .
You must be the King of the Swing .
You made a reservation under " King of the Swing ? "
- Yeah , of course , my horse . - l 'm sorry .
- He doesn 't get out of his cage much . - l can see that .
Here are your keys .
You leave your passports at the desk .
That was taken when I was like 1 3 . I was kind of husky .
Not anymore , though , you know ?
Do you have any private rooms ? We 're probably gonna need them .
The rooms are semiprivate , so you will have roommates .
Roommates , huh ? That 's gay .
Sorry .
- Oh , my God . - It 's okay .
The room is yours . We are going to the spa .
You should come .
Spa .
Jugs .
- Hey . - Hello .
Oh , Jesus .
- Hi . Hey . - Hi .
How you doing ?
I 'm so happy I shaved my balls .
What ? I have the smoothest balls in Iceland .
- You wanna see ? - No , no , no , you 're not- - l 'm good .
Put your anteater away , it 's totally creepy .
- You 're not from Iceland , no ? - No . Fuck , no . American .
Yeah , unlike him , I had my foreskin removed at birth .
Hygiene and- - Am I talking ?
- l 'm Josh . - Natalya .
- And this is Svetlana . - Hi .
Hi , I 'm Paxton .
- And this is Oli . - The King of the Swing .
Hello .
Face on the ass . Never gets old .
Jesus .
So where are you girls from ?
I 'm from Italy , but my parents are Russian .
Prague .
Prague 's cool . Kafka .
So , Natalya ... .
- Yeah ? - You 're Russian , eh ?
Oh , my God . Look , there are too many girls .
- This is awesome . - Yes .
I mean , I was a senior , you know , she was a junior
and then I graduated , and it was weird , you know .
I mean , I 'm totally over it . It 's- - You know , it 's cool .
It 's okay .
Look , Vala is here .
- Who ? - Vala , from front desk.Vala.
- All right , Oli . - Hey , I told you , man .
I 'm the King of the Swing .
Come , let 's dance .
- Does the cigarette bother you ? - No , it 's- -
l put away .
It 's fine , I ... .
l 'm gonna go get some fresh air .
But I 'll be back , okay ?
Cigarette .
Aren 't you a little young ?
- Dollar . - What ?
Dollar .
- Dollar . - Here you go .
Here , children commit the most crime .
They don 't care . They will attack anyone .
- You 're okay ? - Yeah , yeah . Thank you .
Hey , let me buy you a drink .
- Yeah ? - Yeah .
Hey , Josh .
Faggot .
Go with your friends . It 's okay .
I wanted to say sorry about earlier .
About the way I reacted .
We cool ?
I would have done the same thing at your age .
It 's not easy
but from my experience
choosing to have a family was the right choice for me .
Now I have my little girl
who means more to me than anything in the world .
But you should do
whatever 's right for you .
Excuse me , it 's my turn now .
Should we be doing this with them there ?
Yeah , it 's okay .
- Yeah , baby . Josh , give it to me , baby . - Okay , all right . Okay , stop !
- All right . - Come on , big boy .
- We go to spa . - Spa .
Spa , spa , spa . Being dirty while getting clean .
Bye .
Mission accomplished .
You know that Amsterdam kid with the thing on his lip ?
I 'm gonna send him a really nice thank-you note .
Be quiet .
They 're showering together .
Shit , man . We 're never leaving here .
I guess Oli 's not back yet .
No , dude , he probably took that desk girl home .
We 'll see him at breakfast .
- What 's the name ? - Oli Eriksson , 237 .
How are we supposed to understand this without subtitles ?
Fucking gay .
Yeah , he checked out this morning .
You mean he took his passport to go out ?
No , it say he checked out this morning .
- When this morning ? - l don 't know exact time .
I could find out tomorrow .
Hey , Oli , it 's Pax . Are you still with that chick ?
Can I leave a note in case he comes back ?
Okay , cool . Yeah .
All right .
He 's probably still withVala . When she call me , I call you , okay ?
Okay .
- We see you later , right ? - Yeah .
- Bye-bye . - Bye .
Oli , hey , it 's me again . We 're gonna go into town , so call us .
You 're gay . Damn voice mail again .
- Hi ! Hi ! Hi ! - Hi .
Your friend .
- What the hell ? - Your friend , my friend .
What does that say ?
Sayonara . Your friend .
What , they left ? Like , together ?
That doesn 't make any sense . Oli doesn 't even like Asian girls .
I mean , no offence , but- -
When did she send this to you ?
This picture . Today ?
Could you do me a favour and send this picture to my phone ?
This picture .
That water looks fucking cold .
You know , if you fell in , you 'd die in 90 seconds .
Dude , did I tell you I saw a girl drown when I was 8 ?
- Where ? - Lake Michigan .
It was fucked up , man . This little girl , probably 4 or 5 .
We made eye contact , which was a weird thing , you know
and she was yelling for me to help her .
Yeah ? What did you do ?
I ran to the lifeguard , who was busy talking to her boyfriend at the time
and I yelled , you know , " There 's this girl drowning . "
And she couldn 't see her . Probably thought I was making it up .
And then a second later all you could hear was this horrible screaming .
It was that little girl 's mother , dude .
Her kid was dead .
- Jesus . - l had nightmares for years after that .
I mean , I 'd wake up every fucking night hearing that mother scream .
I just ... .
l just felt like I could have done more .
You did the right thing . Could 've been a double drowning .
Yeah , well , I didn 't see it that way at the time .
All I knew was this little girl was dead and her mother 's life was ruined .
What makes you think of this now ?
Bubble gum .
- Sorry , kid . - No , no . Give him some .
What are you doing ?
These fucking kids are dangerous .
Hey , Oli .
- Hey , Oli . - Hey .
- Hey . - Hey .
- Hey , Oli . Hey ! - Oli !
It 's your lucky day , Josh .
A museum .
How 's it hanging ?
- What the fuck ? - Holy shit .
- He got you . - Yeah , that 's hilarious .
Okay .
Hey , Oli .
Hey , hey .
Excuse me ?
I 'm sorry , I thought you were someone else .
Well , I 'm not .
Where did you get that jacket ?
- Hey , I 'm talking to you , man . - Get your fucking hands off me .
This is my jacket .
It 's from Oli .
" l go home " ?
I don 't know , maybe his battery died .
Hey , Kana , when are you leaving ?
I 'm sorry . When are you going away ?
Tomorrow , I go .
Okay , because we may go too .
Do you wanna go to the train with us ? To the train station ?
Tomorrow , train ?
Yeah , yeah .
- Hello , Josh . - Hey .
- Hey . - Come , we go for disco ?
Actually , I just wanna find my friend and get the fuck out of here .
Okay , we 'll see you .
Hey , guys , hold up a sec . We 'll be right out .
Okay .
- Josh , come here , dude . - Yeah , what ?
It 's not their fault Oli disappeared , so stop acting like it is .
- l 'm annoyed he 'd ditch us . - l 'm pissed too .
But we 're not in America .
I mean , people meet each other and split without saying shit .
It 's just how they do it over here .
As well as we may think we know Oli , we don 't really know him .
He could 've gone somewhere with that girl .
Fuck , maybe he 's in Iceland . The guy 's got a daughter .
So let 's look at our options .
We can A , fuck these girls one more night and then head to Barcelona
or B , not fuck them , then head to Barcelona anyway .
Think about it . When I 'm studying for the bar and you 're writing your thesis
this is the shit we 're gonna think about .
Okay . All right , he doesn 't show up , it 's his problem .
- It 's his problem . - All right .
All right .
Hey , Kana , you wanna go to the disco with us ?
You know , disco ? Dancing ?
No ?
Josh ?
- l 'm gonna go back . - Are you okay ?
I 'm , like- - l 'm tired .
Actually , I have , like , a headache .
If you want , I will go with you .
No , no , no , I 'll just see you back at the room .
Goodbye .
Fucking pussy .
- Josh . - Vala .
You don 't look well .
- No , l- - - Here , let me help you .
I feel sick .
Where is ... ? Where is Oli ?
You need rest .
Where 's the restroom ?
Past the bar , in the back .
You guys cool ?
- Vodka Red Bull . - Vodka Red Bull , danke .
Yeah .
Hey !
Open the door .
Oh , fuck .
What the f- - ?
What ... ? Who are you ?
What the f- - ? Where the fuck am I ?
What the fuck is this shit ?
Please , please- - Fuck . Please , please , please- -
l didn 't fucking do shit to you , what the fuck !
Please , please , what the- - ?
Please , no , sir . Please fucking stop . Please !
What the fuck ?
Please , I didn 't fucking do anything .
What the fuck ? This is such fucking bullshit .
What the fuck is this ?
What ? No ! No , please don 't- - !
What the- - ? No , no , fucking don 't you- - No , no !
Oh , my God , no , no ! Oh , my fucking God !
Oh , my God ! No , no , no , no !
Oh , please . What the fuck ?
No , no , no , no , fuck ! No !
Fuck ! Oh , fuck !
You .
Why ?
I always wanted to be a surgeon
but the boards wouldn 't pass me .
Can you guess why ?
You see ?
So I went into business
but business is so boring .
You buy things , you sell them . You make money , you spend money .
What kind of life is that ?
A surgeon
he holds the very essence of life in his hands .
Your life .
He touches it .
He has a relationship with it .
He 's part of it .
Please , please . Just let me go , please .
You want to go ?
is that what you want ?
Oh , my God !
Fuck ! Oh , fuck !
You are free to go .
Oh , fuck . No !
No . No , fuck . No , fuck- -
Please , I have money . I 'll fucking pay you .
Ten times , two times , whatever you want- -
- Pay me ? - Yes .
No one is paying me .
In fact , I am the one paying them .
Relax . Relax , bro .
Oh , shit .
- Two thirty-seven , please . - Two three seven .
Didn 't you check out ?
No , not yet .
Not yet .
- This your bag ? - Yeah .
The maid brought it here . You 're checked out .
- l didn 't check out . - It says .
It happened this morning .
This is bullshit . Did somebody leave a note ?
Because I didn 't fucking check out , dude .
No , man , just this bag . If it 's a mistake- -
Yeah , it 's definitely a mistake . We need a fucking room .
Chill out , man . You 're on vacation .
Two three seven .
Hey , was there a Japanese girl waiting in the lobby for somebody ?
No , think they left this morning .
Yeah .
I 'm sorry , dude .
Oh , I 'm sorry . Excuse me .
It 's okay . We are going to the spa .
You will join us ?
You should come .
Hey , Josh , call me soon as you get this , man .
I got locked in that club . It was retarded , dude .
I 'm at the hostel .
Svetlana !
Hey !
You little fucker .
Jesus .
Wait at hostel for your friends .
They will look for you there no matter what .
Yeah , I know . But , see , my friend Josh is the kind of guy who- -
He just wouldn 't check out without so much as leaving a note , you know .
He 's the responsible one .
Yeah , but maybe he worried his belongings get stolen
so he take them when he go out .
Someone misplace if he leaves note .
It is not uncommon .
Yeah , well , is there anything else that I can do ?
There 's nothing right now .
We have his picture
if we see him , or he is picked up , or something happen
we contact you at hostel , yeah ?
Okay .
Where are you from ?
California .
You are so far from home .
Paxton . Come , have a drink .
Hello , Mr. American .
- Did you get my messages ? - Which one ?
There are so many .
I call you back , but child answer .
Yeah , I know .
Have you seen Josh ?
In English , please .
He is with your friend
the King of the Swing .
- He 's with Oli . - Why you leave last night ?
Did you not listen to my messages ? I got locked in a storage room .
I don 't know , I got sick and passed out .
- What ? - She said you met another girl .
Where are my friends ?
The art show .
- You mean like a museum ? - No , no , no .
Not museum . They went- - How you say , for artist ?
- Exhibit . - Exhibit for artist .
No , that doesn 't make any sense .
Why ? What is wrong ?
Well , they didn 't leave a note . They didn 't call or do anything .
They tell us to tell you .
Yeah , but I tried calling them all day .
Yes , but their phone , the battery die and they do not have- -
How you say , for electricity ?
Converter . Okay , whatever , where is this art show
because I wanna go .
- Have a drink . - l don 't want a drink .
All right ? I wanna see some art .
Okay ? So can we go ?
You 're not going ?
I 've seen this show .
You want gum ?
No .
Too bad for you .
We are here .
Are you coming or what ?
Excuse me . Excuse me .
How is it in there ?
Be careful .
Why is that ?
You could spend all your money
in there .
How much is it ?
For you , free .
There .
That 's the show ?
Yes .
- What ? - Nothing .
You 're so serious , Mr. Serious American .
You fucking whore .
You fucking bitch .
You fucking bitch !
I get a lot of money for you
and that make you my bitch .
Fuck . Get the fuck off me !
This is fucked !
Get the fuck off me !
Fuck .
Talk .
Talk . Speak .
What the fuck do you want me to say ?
American .
No . No , wait !
I 'm not fucking American !
I 'm not fucking- - Look at me . I 'm not fucking American .
American .
Please , what the fuck is this ?
Let me go . Please .
I promise I won 't tell anybody .
Just please let me go .
Don 't . Don 't .
Please don 't .
Don 't , please .
God .
Oh , please , stop !
Please stop it . Please stop it .
I know you don 't wanna do this .
Please don 't do this .
Fuck .
Oh , shit .
What the fuck ?
What do you think ?
How do I look ?
I feel like a butcher or a surgeon or some shit , know what I mean ?
I feel fucking ridiculous in this thing , but I guess you need it , huh ?
Yeah. I 'll tell you something ... .
- Excuse me . Excuse me . - Wait a sec .
How was it ?
Good .
Well , goddamn , motherfucker , for this money , it better be . Shit .
What did you go for , a local ?
What , European ?
- American . - An Amer- - ?
Ain 't that a bitch . Big spender . I fucking- - l love it .
I just fucking love that shit . You know what they got for me ?
They told me they lined up something special .
I 've been waiting almost a week for this shit .
For 50 grand , she better be worth it .
But it 's supposed to be a real rush , right ?
It 's like- - They told me it 's like a real fucking rush , right ?
Come here .
I 've been all over the world . You know , I 've been everywhere .
And the bottom line is , pussy 's pussy .
You know , every strip club , every whorehouse , every ... .
It 's all the same shit .
I just fucked a girl two days ago , I don 't even remember the colour of her tits .
But this , this is something you never forget , right ?
Right ?
- Never . - Never , right .
Let me show you something . Pretty sweet . Check this out .
What do you think of this ? Come on , let me see yours .
Come on , let me see yours . We 're all in the same club .
I 'll be out in a second , guy .
Can I ask you something personal ? Do you mind ?
How 'd you do it ?
Did you do it real slow
or did you just get it over with right away ?
That 's why I asked for the fucking gun .
Because I just wanted to fucking do it quick .
I just wanted to get it over with .
But now I 'm thinking maybe I wanna feel it , you know ?
I wanna fucking feel that shit .
So I don 't know what to- - l 'm thinking- - What do you think I should do ?
- Make it quick . - Make it quick .
Yes .
Yeah , that 's- - No , fuck that shit .
Fuck this , too fucking American , dude . I 'm going fucking old school .
Who wants this , motherfucker ?
Who wants this shit ? Come on , motherfucker .
Bring it .
Hey , buddy .
Get your own fucking room . I paid for this .
What are you , fucking deaf ?
Kana .
- Oh , my God . - What do you want me to do , Kana ?
What ? I don 't understand what you 're saying . What ?
Fuck. I 'm sorry , I 'm sorry . Hold still . Hold still .
- Fuck . Oh , God . God . - No . No !
- Shit . - No !
I 'm sorry. I 'm sorry. I 'm sorry .
Fuck !
We 're gonna get the fuck out of here , Kana .
Move this fucking truck !
Fuck .
We 're almost there .
Oh , my God .
Oh , no .
Fuck .
Kana .
Come here .
No . No , Kana . Kana .
No , Kana .
No , thank you . I prefer to use my hands .
I believe people have lost their relationship with food .
They do not think :
" This is something who gave its life so I would not go hungry . "
I like to have a connection with something that died for me .
Oh , Jesus .
Goddamn !
Fucker .
No , please !
I get a lot of money for you
and that make you my bitch .